https://www.carpecarpio.com/terms/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
We respect your right to privacy. At CarpeCarpio.com we collect only the information necessary for us to complete your order or to contact you regarding the status of your order. The information we collect includes your name, email address, IP, shipping address, billing address and credit card for payment. CarpeCarpio.com will not rent or sell your name or personal information without your permission.
Your email address may also be collected via subscribing to CarpeCarpio.com’s newsletter with the “Subscribe to product updates/news!” form seen below. This newsletter is strictly to inform subscribers of any product updates or news surrounding CarpeCarpio.com. Subscribing is done through a double opt-in process to insure that the email address entered belongs to you. The service used for the newsletter is provided by Bravenet.com, a third-party provider with their own privacy policy. As stated above the form, remember to check or uncheck any options you wish to receive/not receive from Bravenet.com.
The CarpeCarpio.com site contains links to other sites. CarpeCarpio.com is not responsible for the privacy practices and/or the content of such Web sites. When visiting such sites, we urge you to be an informed surfer and use caution when providing any personal data.
CarpeCarpio.com reserves the right to update this privacy policy at anytime.
Security
Added online security to protect your personal information from unauthorized use is provided by using advanced SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption. To assist you in recognizing secure areas of the CarpeCarpio.com web site, a small lock icon will appear in the lower frame of your web browser, starting with the page for credit card number entry. When this icon is present, and in the locked position, you know that information on that page will be secured. The shopping cart and the secure server is provided by Mal’s E-Commerce.
